

Dmytro Lazarenko

FRONTEND DEVELOPER Email: Lazarenkodmitr@gmail.com LinkedIn

GitHub

WhatsApp, Telegram:

+38 098 11 911 77

Weimar, Germany Ready to work remotely / move

I'm fresh in Software Development with 1 year of practice in Frontend. Looking for professional opportunities, where I can improve my skills and get better every day. Aiming at creating responsive websites and web apps. Got experience in working with JavaScript, Typescript, React, HTML, CSS, Preprocessors. I'm studying for a technical qualification - computer engineering

SKILLS

Typescript, JavaScript (ES2015 - 2019)
React, Redux
HTML5, CSS3, Sass (SCSS), BEM,
Bulma Photoshop, Figma
Git/Github, VS Code
Basic OOP understanding

LANGUAGES

English: Strong Intermediate (B1+) Polisch: Strong Intermediate (B1+)

Ukrainian: Proficiency (C2) German: Intermediate (B1)

EDUCATION

National Technical University

Master's degree in computer engineering and automation

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

Frontend course at Mate academy (Git, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, React, Web) 10.2022 - 10.2023

FreeCodeCamp (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer,
Training projects, Januar 2023 - Present
Technologies: JavaScript, React, Typescript,
HTML, CSS, BEM
My Portfolio

Manager of the supply department of network fuel stations / Gemini espresso

Kyiv, Ukraine 08.2016 - 10.2022

Organized work with the supply, maintenance and regular deliveries coffee and coffee maschinen to 400 petrol stations in Ukraine. Supply of equipment and work with chain clients in FMCG market. Record-keeping SRM.

Launching new profitable projects, supporting existing projects.

Cooperate with wholesalers and foreign suppliers of equipment.

Sales of over 60 tons of coffee per year. The highest sales results in the department.

Constant teamwork

Electrical Engineer / Grupa Reesco

Warsaw, Poland 09.2015 - 06.2016

Engineering projects of led lighting, electrical engineering, internet networking, alarm system and energy efficient technology